♪I want to take control of my own future♪
♪أريد أن أتحكم في مستقبلي♪
♪I want to fight back and break this silence♪
♪أريد أن أقاوم وأكسر هذا الصمت♪
♪My fate needs no pity♪
♪مصيري لا يحتاج إلى الشفقة♪
♪Let them witness my glorious moment♪
♪دعهم يشهدون لحظتي المجيدة♪
=Princess Revenge=
=انتقام الأميرة=
=Episode 24=
=الحلقة 24=
Do you know about diamond burials?
هل تعرف عن دفن الماس؟
After cremation, 2% carbon remains
بعد حرق الجثث، تبقى نسبة 2% من الكربون
in human ashes,
في رماد الإنسان،
which can be refined into diamonds.
والتي يمكن تحويلها إلى الماس.
It's true that I'm with Yunzhou.
إنه صحيح أنني مع يونزو.
And this is Yunzhou.
وهذا هو يونزو.
(I'm the female lead in this novel.)
(أنا البطلة الأنثى في هذه الرواية.)
(Why is my story)
(لماذا قصتي)
(all garbled now?)
(كل شيء مشوه الآن؟)
Yunzhou!
يونتشو!
I'm so scared.
أنا خائفة جداً.
I think this world is all fake.
أعتقد أن هذا العالم كله مزيف.
But my love for you is true.
ولكن حبي لك حقيقي.
Since you love me so deeply,
لأنك تحبني بعمق،
could you do me this one last favor?
هل يمكنك أن تفعل لي هذه الخدمة الأخيرة؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
I'll do anything for you.
سأفعل أي شيء من أجلك.
Ye Yunzhou was the beloved
كان يي يون تشو هو المحبوب
you were with all this time.
كنت معك طوال هذا الوقت.
How could you kill him?
كيف يمكنك قتله؟
He was nothing but mere words.
لم يكن سوى مجرد كلمات.
I'm the female lead in the novel.
أنا البطلة الأنثى في الرواية.
Career.
حياة مهنية.
Wealth.
ثروة.
They all should be mine.
ينبغي أن يكونوا جميعهم ملكي.
He had himself to blame
لقد كان هو من يلوم نفسه
for not dying as set by the plot.
لعدم الموت كما هو منصوص عليه في المؤامرة.
That was why the novel got destroyed.
ولهذا السبب تم تدمير الرواية.
I'm going to restart the plot.
سأبدأ من جديد.
I want everyone
أريد الجميع
to be good and get back on track!
لكي تكون جيدًا وتعود إلى المسار الصحيح!
Dongfang Xi.
دونغفانغ شي.
You should feel lucky
يجب أن تشعر بالحظ
that you've had the Dongfangs' protection.
أنك حصلت على حماية دونغفانغ.
It took me ten years
لقد استغرق الأمر مني عشر سنوات
just to approach you.
فقط للتقرب منك.
Bai Zhitao.
باي زيتاو.
Open your eyes and look around this world.
افتح عينيك وانظر حول هذا العالم.
This is the real world,
هذا هو العالم الحقيقي
not the novel.
ليس الرواية.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
If this were the real world,
لو كان هذا هو العالم الحقيقي،
would Dongfang Yan have just vanished for no reason over the past ten years?
هل كان دونغفانغ يان ليختفي بدون سبب خلال السنوات العشر الماضية؟
I'll destroy the only thought of Dongfang Yan
سأدمر الفكر الوحيد لدونغفانغ يان
that you've been holding on to
الذي كنت متمسكًا به
completely.
بالكامل.
Just like how you ruined my plot.
تمامًا مثلما دمرت مؤامرتي.
Stop it!
اوقفها!
Though you're Dongfang Group's
على الرغم من أنك من مجموعة دونغفانغ
heiress...
وريثة...
Oh, no.
أوه لا.
You're its CEO now.
أنت الرئيس التنفيذي للشركة الآن.
This building
هذا المبنى
belongs to me now.
إنها ملك لي الآن.
I'm the chairman here.
أنا الرئيس هنا.
If you don't want to get fired,
إذا كنت لا تريد أن يتم طردك من وظيفتك،
do as I say.
افعل كما أقول لك.
Take everything away.
خذ كل شئ بعيدا.
I'm from the Dongfang family.
أنا من عائلة دونغفانغ.
Are you sure
هل أنت متأكد
you want to side with her?
هل تريد أن تقف إلى جانبها؟
Supporting characters
الشخصيات الداعمة
only exist to help the leads.
لا وجود لها إلا لمساعدة العملاء المحتملين.
Nothing else matters.
لا شىئ اخر يهم.
In your story,
في قصتك،
they're not the leads.
إنهم ليسوا القادة.
But they're the leads
لكنهم القادة
in their own stories.
في قصصهم الخاصة.
Well,
حسنًا،
these people
هؤلاء الناس
are just referred to as "them"
يشار إليهم فقط باسم "هم"
in the novel.
في الرواية.
And you
وأنت
will be the key piece that revives the novel.
ستكون القطعة الرئيسية التي ستعيد إحياء الرواية.
Just like Ye Yunzhou, you'll sacrifice yourself for me
تمامًا مثل Ye Yunzhou، سوف تضحي بنفسك من أجلي
to restart my story.
لإعادة بدء قصتي.
No!
لا!
I'm still
انا لا أزال
that kind and innocent female lead.
تلك البطلة اللطيفة والبريئة.
And you
وأنت
that villainess
تلك الشريرة
doomed to a tragic end.
محكوم عليها بنهاية مأساوية.
But in someone else's story,
ولكن في قصة شخص آخر،
you're just another "her".
أنت مجرد "هي" أخرى.
Dongfang Xi.
دونغفانغ شي.
Have you heard of this?
هل سمعت بهذا؟
Villains
الأشرار
die from talking too much!
تموت من كثرة الكلام!
But heroes die from arrogance!
ولكن الأبطال يموتون من الغطرسة!
(Addicted to Toxic Love)
(مدمن على الحب السام)
(I can't get rid of this book.)
(لا أستطيع التخلص من هذا الكتاب.)
(And it doesn't burn.)
(ولا يحترق.)
Xi.
شي.
We tried,
لقد حاولنا
but we couldn't destroy this novel.
ولكننا لم نستطع أن ندمر هذه الرواية.
No matter what Dongfang Yan and I did,
بغض النظر عما فعلته أنا ودونغفانغ يان،
we just couldn't get rid of this novel.
لم نستطع التخلص من هذه الرواية.
Who would've thought you, the heroine, could do it?
من كان يظن أنك، البطلة، تستطيعين فعل ذلك؟
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
My kind heroine,
بطلتي الطيبة،
how does it feel to ruin your own story?
كيف تشعر عندما تدمر قصتك الخاصة؟
Dongfang Yan!
دونغفانغ يان!
Thank you for destroying the book
شكرا لك على تدمير الكتاب
and bringing me back.
وإعادتي.
No way.
مستحيل.
I'm the heroine...
أنا البطلة...
Dongfang Yan.
دونغفانغ يان.
I'm returning this world
سأعيد هذا العالم
and myself
وأنا
to you.
لك.
You're done for.
لقد انتهيت.
You vanished for ten years,
لقد اختفيت لمدة عشر سنوات،
without a single explanation.
بدون أي تفسير.
Now you're suddenly home.
الآن أنت فجأة في المنزل.
Mom and Dad will probably kick you out.
من المحتمل أن يقوم أمك وأبيك بطردك.
No matter what happens,
بغض النظر عما يحدث،
I'll take responsibility.
سأتحمل المسؤولية.
What a day it's been.
لقد كان يوما رائعا.
You're back, Yan.
لقد عدت ، يان.
Mom.
أم.
Here, let's have some tea.
هنا، دعونا نشرب بعض الشاي.
Dongfang Chen.
دونغفانغ تشن.
Dongfang Chen!
دونغفانغ تشن!
Don't run!
لا تركض!
Yan.
نعم.
You're back.
لقد عدت.
You're back, Yan.
لقد عدت ، يان.
Yeah, I'm back.
نعم لقد عدت.
I'm not leaving again.
لن أغادر مرة أخرى.
It's rare to have the whole family together.
من النادر أن تجتمع العائلة بأكملها معًا.
Forget about
انسى الأمر
the tea.
الشاي.
Get me that bottle of wine I've been keeping.
احضر لي زجاجة النبيذ التي احتفظت بها.
That one.
هذا.
Hurry.
عجل.
Yes.
نعم.
We've got to drink tonight.
علينا أن نشرب الليلة.
Talk some sense into your dad, Xi.
تحدث مع والدك بمنطقية، شي.
I've been reluctant to drink it.
لقد كنت مترددة في شربه.
But I'm happy tonight.
ولكنني سعيد الليلة.
Coming.
آت.
Is it the one, Mom?
هل هي هي يا أمي؟
That's the one.
هذا هو.
It's my precious one.
إنها حبيبتي.
Come on.
تعال.
We'll have it today.
سيكون لدينا ذلك اليوم.
Let's just do as Dad says.
دعونا نفعل فقط كما يقول أبي.
One, two.
واحد، اثنان.
(The End)
(النهاية)
♪I like to live on a happy planet♪
♪أحب أن أعيش على كوكب سعيد♪
♪There's a tide. Raise your head and follow me. Refuse to sleepwalk♪
♪هناك مدّ. ارفع رأسك واتبعني. ارفض السير أثناء النوم♪
♪I can shout Yo for myself♪
♪أستطيع أن أصرخ "يو" لنفسي♪
♪Nothing can stop me♪
♪لا شيء يستطيع إيقافي♪
♪Reach out your hand. Who loves too much to let go?♪
♪مد يدك. من يحب كثيرًا فلا يتخلى عنه؟♪
♪Let's work together to achieve our dreams♪
♪دعونا نعمل معًا لتحقيق أحلامنا♪
♪Go after it. Don't wait♪
♪اسعى وراءه. لا تنتظر♪
♪Time has long told me that it waits for no one♪
♪لقد أخبرني الزمن منذ فترة طويلة أنه لا ينتظر أحدًا♪
♪Enjoy every encounter and feel the night and day♪
♪استمتع بكل لقاء واشعر بالليل والنهار♪
♪Sometimes I stay with both troubles and sorrow♪
♪أحيانًا أبقى مع المشاكل والحزن♪
♪Nostalgia doesn't mean conservative♪
♪الحنين لا يعني التحفظ♪
♪Thoughts are like the universe♪
♪الأفكار مثل الكون♪
♪Not just on stage and behind the scenes♪
♪ليس فقط على المسرح وخلف الكواليس♪
♪Reach out my hands. Who loves the most to let go?♪
♪ أمد يدي. من يحب أن يتخلى عنك أكثر؟♪
♪Wait, wait. Don't wait any longer♪
♪انتظر، انتظر. لا تنتظر أكثر من ذلك♪
♪My dream is waiting for me to pursue it♪
♪حلمي ينتظرني لأسعى لتحقيقه♪
♪I wander like a duck♪
♪أتجول مثل البطة♪
♪An amphibious player♪
♪لاعب برمائي♪
♪I'm not great, but I'm really gentle♪
♪أنا لست عظيمًا، لكنني لطيف حقًا♪
♪I like to live on a happy planet♪
♪أحب أن أعيش على كوكب سعيد♪
♪There's a tide. Raise your head and follow me. Refuse to sleepwalk♪
♪هناك مدّ. ارفع رأسك واتبعني. ارفض السير أثناء النوم♪
♪I can shout Yo for myself♪
♪أستطيع أن أصرخ "يو" لنفسي♪
♪Nothing can stop me♪
♪لا شيء يستطيع إيقافي♪
♪I like to live on a happy planet♪
♪أحب أن أعيش على كوكب سعيد♪
♪There's a tide. Raise your head and follow me. Refuse to sleepwalk♪
♪هناك مدّ. ارفع رأسك واتبعني. ارفض السير أثناء النوم♪
♪I can shout Yo for myself♪
♪أستطيع أن أصرخ "يو" لنفسي♪
♪Nothing can stop me♪
♪لا شيء يستطيع إيقافي♪